Viewers all over the world, you are welcome in the name of Jesus.
Whatever challenges, your affliction, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Affliction - wherever it is located, leave my people!
In the name of Jesus, leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Where can affliction go?
Where can affliction hide?
In the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see the chain has been broken!
I can see the chain of affliction has been broken!
Wherever it is, it has been broken, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, confirm your healing and so shall it be!
Begin to confirm your healing!
I am healed!
Begin to confess your healing right now and get released.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 28/09/2018